<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Whit Huntley</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Whit Huntley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:39:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:39:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>I learn through doing, so these projects stand to show my abilities more than official certifications. Each one I&amp;rsquo;ve done is a functional, holistic application (albeit, not with a high level of polish).
Dotfile Docker Stack Server Stack is a project done with the end goal of making a fully independant web presence, i.e. done entirely without reliance on AWS or other cloud services. The only service which isn&amp;rsquo;t directly provided is domain names, which have to come from ICANN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Hugo!</title>
      <link>/blog/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hello/</guid>
      <description>Good god this website changes a lot.
Starting as a hacked-together hand written set of HTML documents in 2017, it seems to&amp;rsquo;ve annualy gone through a major facelift. First to Vuepress site (for which archives for don&amp;rsquo;t really work). Now I&amp;rsquo;m happy to be able to announce v3.0, entirely in hugo, now with a cool blog-thing which I hope I can use now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Résumé</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 14:09:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description> If you would like a copy of my resume, it is available below in odt and pdf formats. Please note that they have been modified to remove contact information I don&amp;rsquo;t want floating around on the internet. if you have a business inquiry please email me (address is availble on my homepage).
 Résumé Documents ©2019 Whit Huntley, All rights reserved.
 EOF </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The GNU/AGPL v3.0 License (Full Text)</title>
      <link>/licenses/gnu-agpl_30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 13:35:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/licenses/gnu-agpl_30/</guid>
      <description>Return to Licenses GNU AFFERO GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 19 November 2007
Copyright &amp;copy; 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. https://fsf.org/
Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
Preamble The GNU Affero General Public License is a free, copyleft license for software and other kinds of works, specifically designed to ensure cooperation with the community in the case of network server software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Creative Commons BY-NC-SA 4.0 Intl License (Full Text)</title>
      <link>/licenses/cc-by-nc-sa_40intl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 13:35:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/licenses/cc-by-nc-sa_40intl/</guid>
      <description>Return to Licenses Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International ======================================================================= Creative Commons Corporation (&amp;quot;Creative Commons&amp;quot;) is not a law firm and does not provide legal services or legal advice. Distribution of Creative Commons public licenses does not create a lawyer-client or other relationship. Creative Commons makes its licenses and related information available on an &amp;quot;as-is&amp;quot; basis. Creative Commons gives no warranties regarding its licenses, any material licensed under their terms and conditions, or any related information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensing Info</title>
      <link>/licensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 13:10:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/licensing/</guid>
      <description>As a matter of principle, and in the respect of the freedom of ideas, all software and documents which I can claim ownership of are (unless otherwise noted) licensed under the GNU Affero General Public License v3.0 xor the Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International license respectively.
The Aribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International (CC BY-NC-SA 4.0) License Summary This is a human-readable summary of (and not a substitute for) the license:
Rights The CC BY-NC-SA 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 13:10:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World! I&amp;rsquo;m Whit Huntley a student, programmer, and activist.
OpenPGP Key   2CE2 F0FA 3F3E 8078 1544 7A06 B5B5 EEA4 64CA 97AB
 Programming I started programming in 2012 at a Java+Scratch summer class for my parents to get me out of the house for a change. While what I wrote there was absolutely abhorrent, I loved the theory and wanted to pursue it further.
In 2013, I began attending SkilStak Coding Arts where I learned the essentials of Python 3, Golang, and nebulous Linux things (bash, vim, ssh, git, and so on).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acknowledgements</title>
      <link>/acknowledgements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 12:12:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/acknowledgements/</guid>
      <description>Here are acknowledgments and licensing info about this site.
This site is built with hugo, and the template a modified version of the theme rhazdon/hugo-theme-hello-friend-ng.
The content on this site, unless otherwise stated, is licensed under the CC BY-NC-SA 4.0 license and GNU/AGPL3 license. More information about my licenses are available here and this website&amp;rsquo;s source code is available at Git@Dotfile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schoolwork Portal</title>
      <link>/edu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 11:55:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/edu/</guid>
      <description>This is the hub for all of my works done for my school classes. All work is licensed under the Creative Commons BY-NC-SA 4.0 Intl license or the The GNU Affero General Public License v3.0. (learn more about licensing)
 Go to Current Classes This contains a link to all of my current work for the current semester. If a file is missing or you need access to an older archive, please get in touch via email!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>